JACEK SUPERNAK

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Innovative Frontend Developer Focused on cutting edge, mobile first design

- nidden for website version
- Q Dublin, Ireland
- https://supernak.me

ABOUT ME

I excel in crafting mobile-first, responsive web designs, with a strong focus on modern development practices. I have over 2 year of professional experience including TeamForward, Chingu and freelance projects, utilising JS frameworks, various modern styling technologies, unit testing, and Agile methodology.

SKILLS

JavaScript ES6 | TypeScript | ReactJS | NextJS | Tailwind | Styled Components | S(CSS) | HTML5 | Git | Jest | ExpressJS | NodeJS | Figma | Agile/Scrum

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer at TeamForward

November 2023 - present

- Collaborated in a dynamic remote team, developing innovative web solutions using Next.js, React.js, Express.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Socket.io, Tailwind, and TypeScript, spanning across 3 continents and multiple time zones.
- Led the development of location-based features, integrating the Mapbox library for profile location setting and users filtering on the main dashboard.
- Conceptualized and implemented a welcoming user journey for new signups, including personalized welcome messages and initial profile location setup prompts.

Front-End Developer at Chingu

January 2022 - June 2023

- Utilized a diverse technology stack including HTML5, JavaScript ES6, CSS, MongoDB, Express, ReactJS, NodeJS, Redux, and Sockets.io.
- Coded user interfaces based on Figma designs, particularly for signup/login and chat functionalities.
- Implemented user authentication, data validation, and data handling mechanisms.
- Designed and developed UI components such as a radio search form and search results, incorporating backend data fetching.
- Consistently managed project backlogs in ZenHub.
- Worked collaboratively and productively in a scrum/agile team environment across all projects.

Freelance

January 2021 - January 2022

• Created websites for individual clients according their specifications.

EDUCATION

2010 - 2011 | Wroclaw University of Technology, Computer Science